{
    "id": "5c6ac14ed6584b0d997f7b6207ac3c28",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She speaks English well, …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does she",
                "doesn't she",
                "hasn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b5a1baf41a394f659f1f6527ffc74e95"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has left, ………………… ..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has he",
                "hasn't he",
                "doesn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "128151e928514b6cb6f3922f3692735e"
        },
        {
            "question": "You will have some tea, ……………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will you",
                "haven't you",
                "won't you"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d1ef247890334b8fa22680ae81de66d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I need not stay long, …………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "need I",
                "needn't I"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fff1f0531954493a99b9e0c2bb20733b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She loves dancing, ………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does she",
                "doesn't she",
                "has she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "26d7de763e7745ed87981d221a6c35ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are not joining the strike, …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are you",
                "aren't you",
                "have you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5bc79ffc117b42e285b45e0d57898f30"
        },
        {
            "question": "He broke the glass, ………………… .?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did he",
                "didn't he",
                "hadn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a1e494de6ec4b149b2f159b7d638bdc"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not late, ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is he",
                "isn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a7c26038cdf64f529c610e48a63a858c"
        },
        {
            "question": "He used to play cricket when he was young, ………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did he",
                "didn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6fb930b32e0a4ef0bd417faefd266956"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s take some rest, …………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall we",
                "should we",
                "will we"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dc120e7e735b44168f611d529dd14ccb"
        }
    ]
}